In the previous video, we carefully wrote down the steps we followed in working
在之前的视频中，我们仔细地写下了
a specific case by hand.
手工处理特定案例时所遵循的步骤。
In this video, we generalize the steps to finding the closest point.
在本视频中，我们概括了寻找最近点的步骤。
Looking at our steps, some of them are similar, but
看看我们的步骤，其中一些是相似的，但
we need to make them match up.
我们需要让它们匹配。
Each of these colored boxes contain similar steps.
每个彩色方框都包含相似的步骤。
First a computation, then a comparison.
首先是计算，然后是比较。
We also have some steps we only do sometimes, and
我们还有一些只有有时才做的步骤，
we need to figure out under what conditions we do them.
我们需要弄清楚我们在什么条件下执行这些步骤。
We also have some steps we only do at the start and the end, and
我们还有一些步骤只能在开头和结尾做，
we're going to need to generalize the numbers in those.
我们需要对这些步骤中的数字进行概括。
So the first thing let's do is make these similar stuffs match up.
因此，让我们做的第一件事就是让这些相似的东西相匹配。
Why are computing 9 squared plus 6 squared here,
为什么在这里计算 9 平方加 6 平方，
7 squared plus -1 squared next and so on.
接下来计算 7 平方加上 -1 平方等等。
If we look at our picture, the 9 comes from delta x and the 6 comes from delta y.
如果我们看一下我们的图片，9 来自 delta x，6 来自增量 y。
The difference between the point the point 10, 5 in set S and 1, -1, the point p.
集合 S 中的点 10、5 和 1、-1、点 p 之间的差异。
The same is true for all of these other numbers, the differences in x and
所有这些其他数字也是如此，
y between points s and p.
点 s 和 p 之间的 x 和 y 差异。
So we might rewrite all of these steps to have the points S1,
所以我们可以重写所有这些步骤，让点 S1、
S2, etc., up to S6.
S2 等，直到 S6。当@@
We'll call the first point s0 when we get to the starting step.
我们进入起始步骤时，我们将第一个点称为 s0。
Programmers often like to start counting from 0.
程序员通常喜欢从 0 开始计数。
The first substitution gives us s1's x- P's x quantity squared + s1's
第一个替换给我们 s1 的 x-P 的 x 数量平方 + s1 的
y- P's y quantity squared, then the square root of the whole thing.
y-P 的 y 数量平方，然后是整个事物的平方根。
Now, the result of this computation won't always be 10.82 or 7.07,
现在，这个计算的结果并不总是10.82或7.07，
so we should give these a name, such as current distance.
所以我们应该给它们起个名字，比如当前距离。
But when we do this, we're going to have to keep track of
但是当我们这样做时，
each time we use this number and update them, too.
我们必须跟踪每次使用这个数字并更新它们。
That is if we change the first occurrence of 10.82 to currentDistance,
也就是说，如果我们将第一次出现的 10.82 更改为 currentDistance，
then we need to make this line compare current distance to 8.06.
那么我们需要将这条线的当前距离与 8.06 进行比较。
But some of these numbers are used in other ways, so
但是其中一些数字是以其他方式使用的，因此
these are going to need a different name.
这些数字需要不同的名称。
Here, we've replaced the value for each computation with currentDistance.
在这里，我们将每次计算的值替换为 currentDistance。
Notice that the only times we update the best choice
请注意，只有
are when current distance is smaller.
当当前距离较小时，我们才会更新最佳选择。
That means we must have been keeping track of the best distance so
这意味着我们一定一直在跟踪
far, which we now need to update, as well.
迄今为止的最佳距离，我们现在也需要对其进行更新。
Now, we update the best distance when the current distance is smaller, and
现在，当当前距离较小时，我们会更新最佳距离，
we can use the value of best distance for comparison with future computations.
我们可以使用最佳距离的值与将来的计算进行比较。
Let's look at the first 8.06 we compute and consider the other places it occurs.
让我们来看看我们计算的第一个 8.06，并考虑它发生的其他地方。
The computation can be achieved like the others using S0.
可以像使用 S0 一样进行计算。
Since this is our first computation, it might as well be the best so far,
由于这是我们的第一次计算，它也可能是迄今为止最好的，
then we can replace the other instance with bestDistance, making the steps match.
那么我们可以用 BestDistance 替换另一个实例，使步骤匹配。
To continue generalizing, let's look at the point for
为了继续概括，让我们来看看
best choice 2,7,8,-2, and -3,-5.
最佳选择 2,7,8、-2 和 -3、-5 的重点。
Each of these is the particular point we're looking at so
这些都是我们正在研究的具体点，因此
we can replace those with S0, S2, and S4.
我们可以用 S0、S2 和 S4 替换它们。
Recall that we only updated the best choice when the current distance
回想一下，我们只
was smaller.
是在当前距离较小时才更新最佳选择。
We can make each of these steps the same by including instructions to compare
我们可以通过包括每次比较
current distance and best distance each time, but
当前距离和最佳距离的说明来使每个步骤都相同，但是
only update best distance if current distance is smaller.
只有在当前距离较小时才更新最佳距离。
Now we do the same steps for each of the points.
现在，我们对每个点都执行相同的步骤。
Each colored box is the same as the others, except for
每个彩色盒子都与其他方块相同，唯一的不同
what point we're looking at, S1, S2, through S6.
是我们要看的是什么，从S1、S2到S6。
That means we an express this as a repetition
这意味着我们可以将其表达为重复，
where we count from 1 to the number of points in S exclusive.
其中我们从 1 计数到 S 不包含的分数。
We'll call each number that we count i,
我们将计算的每个数字称为 i，
and we'll compute the distance from the ieth point in S to P.
然后计算从 S 中第 ieth 点到 P 的距离。
If current distance is smaller than best distance,
如果当前距离小于最佳距离，
then we'll update best choice to SI and best distance to current distance.
则我们会将最佳选择更新为 SI，将最佳距离更新为 SI，将最佳距离更新为当前距离。
We haven't changed our steps for the start or end, but
我们没有改变开始或结束的步骤，但
we should generalize the point we give as our answer.
我们应该将我们给出的观点概括为答案。
The answer is not always going to be -3, -5.
答案并不总是-3、-5。
Why did we say that?
我们为什么这么说？
The answer was the best choice when we finished counting, so in general,
当我们完成计数时，答案是最佳选择，所以总的来说，
we'll give an answer of best choice.
我们会给出最佳选择的答案。
The only other thing we need to do is consider a corner case.
我们唯一需要做的另一件事就是考虑一个极端情况。
What if S has 0 points in it?
如果 S 里面有 0 分怎么办？
In that case, we give an answer of no answer exists.
在这种情况下，我们会给出不存在答案的答案。
This corner case was not revealed by the example we just worked, but
我们刚才研究的例子并未揭示这个极端情况，但
it would have come up through testing.
它本来是通过测试得出来的。
Working an example with 0 points,
以 0 分为例，
we would have had a problem doing the first step of our computation.
我们在计算的第一步时会遇到问题。
So we report no answer exists and skip all of these other steps.
因此，我们报告没有答案，请跳过所有其他步骤。
So here is our algorithm.
所以这是我们的算法。
You can test it yourself.
你可以自己测试一下。
Later on, we'll learn how to translate this into code.
稍后，我们将学习如何将其转换为代码。